Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Flowers That Bloom for Me
Episode 37
Your Majesty, it’s terrible!
All our withered leaves have been taken away
I never thought they’d manage to snatch them
Do those Flower Bugs always steal your withered leaves?
Actually, those Flower Bugs used to live on the surface of the mud
We were all doing our own work
But one day
the Flower Bugs suddenly grew in size
and their numbers skyrocketed
They spent all day just eating
and stopped digging or loosening the soil.
There weren’t enough withered leaves outside,
so the Flower Bugs started stealing our food.
From then on, we hid our remaining withered leaves in the burrow
to keep them away.
But to our surprise, they still got stolen.
Planie, did you notice anything odd?
They’re welcoming us so warmly, even though their food is almost all gone.
That’s really nice.
That’s not what I meant.
The sudden increase in the size and number of Flower Bugs…
Don’t you think…
it might be related to the fragment?
Exactly.
Our food supply has been taken away.
What should we do?
There should still be withered leaves in the Withered Leaf Zone.
I’ll go fetch them.
No.
That zone has been overrun by Flower Bugs lately, too.
Right.
We can’t let Your Majesty take that risk alone.
But you’re injured right now.
You can’t beat those Flower Bugs.
Besides, I have a way to retrieve the withered leaves.
Why don’t we go with you?
You are our guests, after all.
There’s no need to put yourselves in danger for us.
Actually, we came down to look for a certain multicolored fragment.
I suspect the changes in the Flower Bugs are linked to that fragment.
We might as well go and take a look.
But those Flower Bugs are formidable.
I’m afraid you might get hurt.
You’re underestimating me.
Not only will I not get hurt,
but I’m also capable of protecting you all.
Compared to that Flower Tribe member who just makes a lot of noise,
I find these two guests much more interesting.
By the way,
that Flower Tribe member seems to have disappeared.
What? Why didn’t you say so sooner?
Could he have been carried off by the bugs?
Hurry and look around for him.
Yes.
Is this the place where Flower Babies look for the Spark?
Mentor Xi Huahua, it looks like you’ve never been here before.
That’s impossible.
I know this place like the back of my hand.
Everyone else has already started.
We’d better hurry.
Xi Huahua.
I hear you’re the most talented flower on the Xilan Tree.
People are just being too kind.
But now that I’m here,
you’ll have to settle for second place.
Because I’m the one who’s truly the best.
Is that so?
Then why don’t we have a contest?
Let’s see whose Flower Baby grasps the Spark first.
Just with your Flower Baby who does nothing but eat…
I, on the other hand, am a Flower Baby with the best potential.
Mentor Mei Huahua
Do you want some?
Where did you get that cake?
Here.
Thanks. You really are a good Flower Baby.
Mentor Mei Huahua
Zhuangzhuang, you aren’t allowed to eat that.
It will lower your Spark.
Okay.
It seems our Flower Babies love to eat just as much.
It looks like Xi Huahua is already competing with Mei Huahua.
This Flower Baby trial is going to be quite a show.
Xi Huahua
Just you wait.
Bring it on, then.
Let’s go.
There are so many Flower Bugs here.
Look.
The withered leaves are over there.
Let’s sneak over and grab them.
And keep an eye out for the fragment while we’re at it.
Why are you using sign language again?
I meant, check for the fragment while we’re at it.
Oh no.
Look, this flower is called a Rocket Flower.
It symbolizes a vibrant life.
Go over there and see if there’s a Spark.
This flower makes me…
Well? Do you feel a connection now?
This flower makes me feel allergic!
It’s not going to be one of those clichés
where they wake up, is it?
How did a flower suddenly appear?
It’s just a flower; it’s fine.
Run!
Let’s try this flower.
This flower won’t work.
I can’t move anymore.
Run!
This is a Laughing Flower.
It has the power to make people happy.
You’re laughing so happily;
does that mean you have a Spark?
I’m laughing at myself.
To think I actually believed a Flower Baby like me could have a Spark.
It’s no use trying.
Maybe they were right.
A Flower Baby like me can never become a flower.
Why give up so easily?
Because you are a genius of the Flower Tribe.
How could you possibly understand an ordinary Flower Baby like me?
I understand.
Look.
Your legs.
I loved playing with my friends,
but I was the slowest runner,
and I fell down easily.
Every time, I could only watch their backs as they ran into the distance.
To catch up with my friends,
I practiced running every day,
falling down and getting back up.
Then, one day…
I became the fastest goat.
I never imagined that you…
used to be just as clumsy as me.
We weren’t clumsy.
I want to tell you…
that with hard work and persistence,
anyone can be a genius!
Let’s give it another try, shall we?
Okay, let’s go.
Are you okay?
This kind of flower is called Bamboo Node.
It can extend and retract at will.
That’s too much.
I’m really angry now.
I’m going to throw it—
You guys go down and get some fresh air.
Xi Huahua, thank you.
A huge withered leaf actually fell down.
There’s one here, too.
Watch out behind you.
I don’t know why, but we’re saved.
All these withered branches—what a lucky break.
Oh no, I’m out of energy right at a moment like this.
Mentor Xi Huahua, save me!
Mentor Mei Huahua!
I’ve obtained a Spark!
That’s amazing! Let’s go celebrate.
Okay.
Lan Baobao, jump over here!
It’s too far; I can’t make the jump.
It’s a Bamboo Node!
Quick, use the Bamboo Node in your hand to jump over!
Lan Baobao, look!
It has sprouted a flower bud.
If we just plant it back in the ground,
it will bloom.
This is my Spark.
Bamboo Node’s flower symbolizes a fresh start.
But no Flower Baby has ever got a Spark from Bamboo Nodes before.
You’re the first one.
Bamboo Node.
What on earth is happening up there?
Things keep falling down.
No matter what’s going on,
it saved our lives, at least.
By the way, did you find that fragment?
When we were fighting the Flower Bugs earlier,
we didn’t find the fragment on them.
Do you know of any other places with Flower Bugs?
Then it has to be the Bug Nest.
The Bug Nest.
What is this place?
To be continued